(Sheldon:)This rock
(Sheldon:)encapsulates
all my negative emotions.
(Sheldon:)I will cast you far away.
(Sheldon:)Feel free to take out a pigeon
while you're at it.
(Leonard:)Let it fly.
(Sheldon:)Ow, ow, ow, ow,
(Sheldon:)ow, ow, ow, ow...
(Amy:)What happened?
(Sheldon:)I tried to let go of anger
(Sheldon:)and threw a rock
into my foot!
(Leonard:)Then he got more angry
and kicked the rock
(Leonard:)with his other foot.
Wha--?
(Penny:)And what happened to you?
(Leonard:)Oh, I laughed so hard,
(Leonard:)I burst a blood vessel
in my nose. It's fine.
(Amy:)You know, it's one thing
to be envious,
(Amy:)but now you're
injuring yourself.
(Amy:)It has to stop.
(Leonard:)Although if you are
gonna do it again,
(Leonard:)please let me know,
so I can get it on video.